https://www.uw360.asia/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
What personal information do we hold?
We hold the following personal information:
Information which you voluntarily provide to us when using this website (including, without limitation, your name, postal address(es), telephone number(s) and e-mail address(es))
Information about your use of this website
For what purposes do we hold personal information?
We hold information which you provide to us for our own administrative, sales, marketing and product/service development purposes.
Depending on the information which you have provided to us, we may contact you by letter, e-mail, fax, telephone or SMS. If you would rather not be contacted by us, please let us know at the address noted below.
Unless you object in writing to us at the time the relevant personal information is collected, you consent to our use of the information set out or referred to in this Privacy Policy.
Unless we have your prior consent, we shall not sell, rent, trade or share any personal information which we hold except that:
We may disclose information which is held by us where required to do so by law or in connection with legal proceedings;
We may disclose aggregate statistics to third parties which are made up from statistics in respect of individual persons but these statistics will not include personally identifying information;
We may disclose personal information to our legal, accounting, marketing or other professional advisers, our website hosts and our courier, postal or transport providers, and insurers (names and addresses only in the latter case);
we may disclose personal information to other companies within the Asian Geographic Magazines group.
Should we wish to use your personal information for a purpose not permitted under this Privacy Policy, we will contact you to seek your consent.
For how long do we hold personal information?
We will not hold on to any personal information for any longer than is reasonably necessary for the purposes noted above
What procedures do we use to protect your privacy?
We undertake to process the personal information which we collect in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws relating to data protection.
We have strict security procedures covering the storage and disclosure of your information (although we do not warrant that this is the case) in order to prevent unauthorised access. This means that we may ask for proof of identity before disclosing personal information to you.
This website contains links to other websites. Equally, other websites may provide links to this website. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies, if any, of each and every website which you use.
Please note that the Internet is not a secure medium. When submitting personal information to us using the Internet, your details may not be secure from access by third parties. The submission of personal information to us using the Internet is therefore made at your own risk.
We will also, on written request from you, amend any personal information which we hold about you. Where we amend the personal information which we hold about you, we will generally retain a copy of the previous version for our records. However, as noted above, we will not hold on to any personal information for any longer than is necessary for the purposes noted above.
You can contact us at the following address:
Webmaster (www.uw360.asia)
20 Bedok South Road
Singapore 469277
Please note that, if you are under 16 years old, you must provide us with the name and address of your parent or guardian. We will let him or her know that you are providing us with personal information and seek any necessary consents from him or her.
Direct marketing
We operate a policy of 100% opt-in marketing. The contact details you provide (such as your telephone number, fax number, postal address and email address) may be used by us to send you information about products and services. Your contact details will not be provided to any third parties for the purposes of direct marketing. Your contact details will only be used in this way if you have previously indicated your consent to receiving such messages.
All marketing messages sent to you by us will contain a statement re-iterating these instructions as to how to opt-out.
Further important points
By entering this website, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy.
If we change our privacy policy while this website remains active, we will post the new Privacy Policy on this website. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 6th August 2010.
We welcome your views about our website and our Privacy Policy. If you would like to contact us with your views, please write to us at the address noted above, or fill out the contact form.
- Advertisement -
Get Connected
Subscribe for more inspiring stories and current news from Underwater 360
Leave this field empty if you're human:
About Underwater360
The platform that offers everything you want and need to know. Bringing entertaining and digestible content loved by our readers, we are aimed at the dive community and its industry.
Advertising
Trade360
Subscribe
Shop
About Us
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Career Opportunities
